https://www.berkshireassociates.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
Berkshire understands the importance of privacy to you. We have adopted this Privacy Policy as it recognizes the rights of visitors to our site to keep their personal contact information private.
What is it?
Your privacy is important to Berkshire. This statement discloses the information practices for Berkshire websites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. We have implemented these practices for the Berkshire website (www.berkshireassociates.com). We have included this information under Privacy Statement at the bottom of every page on Berkshire’s website.
Personal information
In general, you can visit the Berkshire website without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you. You will be asked to give us personal information, such as your name, address, email address, or credit card number. This information is needed in order to correspond with you, to process an order by you, or to provide you with information about our products and services when requested. This information is collected only when necessary.
Information Security and Sharing
Information is only used by Berkshire in order to provide you with information about our products and services or for internal data analysis. Berkshire does not lease, sell, share, or otherwise disclose its visitors’ email addresses to third parties. We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as the use of secured databases and email system, to help us keep your information secure, accurate, current, and complete. This information is available only to Berkshire employees and only when necessary in order to provide information to you.
Cookies
Berkshire uses data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain pages of our site. Cookies enable us to deliver content specific to your interests and keep track of your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our website. After you accept a cookie, it is passed from your browser to our servers each time you request a page. This cookie consists of a unique token that anonymously identifies to the server so that you can more easily access the features of this website. Most cookies are “session cookies,” meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our site.
Personal information
Nemo nibh, condimentum autem ligula ultricies, velit, sociosqu eos voluptatibus modi, porttitor natoque proin proident! Facilisis dapibus convallis molestie fugit, taciti! Itaque! Pharetra alias, animi consectetur? Autem cupidatat incidunt nec! Voluptates illo! Voluptas ligula sodales curabitur.
Information Security and Sharing
Information is only used by Berkshire in order to provide you with information about our products and services or for internal data analysis. Berkshire does not lease, sell, share, or otherwise disclose its visitors’ email addresses to third parties. We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as the use of secured databases and email system, to help us keep your information secure, accurate, current, and complete. This information is available only to Berkshire employees and only when necessary in order to provide information to you.
Cookies
Berkshire uses data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain pages of our site. Cookies enable us to deliver content specific to your interests and keep track of your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our website. After you accept a cookie, it is passed from your browser to our servers each time you request a page. This cookie consists of a unique token that anonymously identifies to the server so that you can more easily access the features of this website. Most cookies are “session cookies,” meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our site.
Business Relationships
The Berkshire website contains links to other web sites. Berkshire is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other such web sites.
Notification of Changes
This privacy statement was last updated in January 2020.
Questions regarding this statement
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the addresses below via email, phone, or in writing:
Email: bai.web@berkshireassociates.com
Phone: 800.882.8904
Berkshire Associates Inc.
Berkshire is a human resources and technology firm specializing in affirmative action, pay equity, and applicant tracking.
